http://www.marshallnewsmessenger.com/site/privacy.html

Home
Our PolicyFor each visitor to the Web site, the Marshall News Messenger servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the domain name (for example, www.marshallnewsmessenger.com) of visitors. This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for Web site traffic audits. We also provide this information (as well as information from third-party market researchers) about our users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our advertisers.The Marshall News Messenger may place a "cookie" on the browser of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. A cookie may be used to tell when your computer has contacted the Web site. The Marshall News Messenger uses the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as delivery of features and advertisements, so the Marshall News Messenger can customize delivery of information to you without compromising privacy. For example, cookies may be used to ensure that you will not see the same banner advertisement too often in a single session.Through your use of the Web site, the Marshall News Messenger may collect information about you that identifies you or your household. Normally, you would provide such information when specifically asked for it by the Marshall News Messenger. Any information in the Marshall News Messenger's possession solely as a result of your use of the Web site and that is associated with you or your household is considered "Personal Information." It consists of both information supplied by you (e.g. name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) and information collected about how you use the Web site (e.g. the fact that you have bought merchandise through the Web site). It does not include aggregate information (e.g. the total number of household users older than 18 years, the zip code in which a user lives) or information that you have made public on the Web site or that is otherwise publicly available.The Marshall News Messenger uses personal information only for purposes necessary to provide the Web site and other products and services to you. These purposes are as follow:to process requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchantsto perform such normal business operations as billing, collecting and accountingto personalize and publicize the Web site based on your interests, including making you aware of editorial features, advertisements and commercial itemsto investigate complaints and to protect the Web site and the Marshall News Messenger, its readers and employees as provided by law or in case of emergency, as determined by legal counsel for the Marshall News Messenger except as necessary to process your requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants featured on the Web siteThe Marshall News Messenger does not rent, sell, barter or give away any lists containing personal information for use by any outside company. The Marshall News Messenger also respects the privacy of data on your personal computer and does not access, read, upload or store data contained in or derived from your private files without your authorization.LINKSThe Marshall News Messenger site contains links to other sites. The Marshall News Messenger is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with the Marshall News Messenger (such as co-branded pages or "powered by" or "in cooperation with" relationships). The Marshall News Messenger does not disclose personally identifiable information or unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you that is not subject to the Marshall News Messenger's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you may visit by linking from the Marshall News Messenger site.OPT OUT PROCEDURESYou always may opt out of receiving future mailings or other information from the Marshall News Messenger. If the mailing does not have an e-mail cancellation form, send e-mail to tmartinez@vicad.com detailing the type of information that you no longer desire to receive.CHILDREN'S PRIVACYThe following additional terms, conditions and notices apply to use of the Web site by children under the age of 13 years whenever the Marshall News Messenger becomes aware that a user is in that age range:Users under 13 years old may not submit or post information on the Web site without the consent of the user's parent or legal guardian. Prior to collecting any personal information about a child under 13, the Marshall News Messenger makes reasonable efforts to obtain consent from the child's parent after informing the parent about the types of information the Marshall News Messenger will collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed.Although the Marshall News Messenger will apply these children's terms and conditions whenever it becomes aware that a user who submits personal information is less than 13 years old, no method is foolproof. The Marshall News Messenger strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission."Personal Information" collected from children may include any of the information defined above as "Personal Information" with respect to general users of the Web site and may be used by the Marshall News Messenger for the same purposes. Except as necessary to process a child's requests or orders placed with advertisers or merchants featured on the Web site, the Marshall News Messenger does not rent, sell, barter or give away any lists containing a child's Personal Information for use by any outside company.If a child enters a game, contest or other activity sponsored by the Marshall News Messenger on the Web site, the child may be required by the Marshall News Messenger to provide the minimum Personal Information reasonably necessary for the child to participate in such activity.A child's parent or legal guardian may request the Marshall News Messenger to provide a description of the Personal Information that the Marshall News Messenger has collected from the child, as well as instruct the Marshall News Messenger to cease further use, maintenance and collection of Personal Information from the child.If a child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address or other personally-identifying information on chat areas, bulletin boards or other forums or public posting areas, such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.GENERALThese terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement and understanding between you and the Marshall News Messenger with respect to use of the Web site, superseding all prior or contemporaneous communications and/or proposals. The Marshall News Messenger reserves the right to make changes to these terms and conditions immediately by posting the changed terms and conditions in this location. By continuing to use the Web site, you are agreeing to all changes made by the Marshall News Messenger. A printed version of these terms and conditions shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to use of the Web site to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.The Web site is controlled and operated by the Marshall News Messenger from its principal office in Marshall, Texas, USA. The Marshall News Messenger makes no representation that materials on the Web site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access the Web site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. The Web site is not intended to subject the Marshall News Messenger to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than the State of Texas and the United States of America.GENERALIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of the Marshall News Messenger, or your dealings with the Marshall News Messenger, you may contact us by clicking here
Sign up for the latest local coronavirus news!
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
Coronavirus Updates from Marshall News Messenger
This email will send daily with the most recent updates of news regarding the Covid-19 coronavirus significant to our area.
Please enter a valid email address.
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
This list sends you an email of our top stories every day.
Sports Digest
Our sports coverage delivered right to your email.
Deals & Promotions
This is the list to receive occasional emails containing special offers, deals and promotions (like contests).
Breaking
Breaking news from The Marshall News-Messenger delivered straight to your inbox.
You must select at least one email list.
Please enter a valid email address.
ArticlesSorry, there are no recent results for popular articles.
ImagesSorry, there are no recent results for popular images.
VideosSorry, there are no recent results for popular videos.
Follow us on Twitter
Tweets by News_Messenger
© Copyright 2020 Marshall News Messenger, 309 East Austin St. Marshall, TX | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
